Guide to the Statler Club records, 1943-1998.
Statler Club records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Statler Club records, 1943-1998.
28-8-1802
Statler Club (Cornell University)
3.6 cubic ft.
Legal documents, printed materials, reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes constitution and bylaws, committee records, correspondence, minutes of the Board of Directors, and other records of the Statler Club, Cornell University. Also, records kept by Charles Sibley, President of the Statler Club, 1957-1958 and records kept by Jane Hardy, 1993-1998.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes constitution and bylaws, committee records, correspondence, minutes of the Board of Directors, and other records of the Statler Club, Cornell University. Also, records kept by Charles Sibley, President of the Statler Club, 1957-1958 and records kept by Jane Hardy, 1993-1998.
Includes bound dinner menus (1950-1953) and luncheon menus (1950-1956) from the Statler Club.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Statler Club (Cornell University); Cornell University -- Societies, etc.; Cornell University
Subjects:
Societies
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Organizing Faculty Club - Correspondence, 1943-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Committee of Seventy, 1944-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bylaws and Agreements, 1944-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors Meetings, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Summary of Operations, Certificate of Incorporation, Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Statements of Profit and Loss, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Membership, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Charles Sibley - President Records, 1950s-1960s (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Statler Standards, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Agreement Between the Statler Club and the Statler Hotel, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- University Club Task Force - Reports to President Rawlings and Provost Martin, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- University Club Task Force Reports, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- History of the Statler Club (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Statler Card and Brochures (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Menus and Napkin, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Operating Criteria, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Board Meeting Minutes, Memos, Budgets, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Board Meeting Minutes, Memos, Budgets, Bylaws, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Board Meeting Minutes, Memos, Budgets, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Board Meeting Minutes, Memos, Budgets, Bylaws, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Board Meeting Minutes, Memos, Memership Lists, Budgets, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Statler Club Dinner Menus - Bound, September 1950-December 1952 (Box 3)
- Statler Club Dinner Menus - Bound, January 1953-August 1956 (Box 4)
- Statler Club Luncheon Menus - Bound, September 1950-April 1956 (Box 5)
- Statler Club Luncheon Menus - Loose Copies (not complete), May 1956-December 1961 (Box 5)